figpin.com 2019-01-03

# Privacy and Terms – FiGPiN

**General Provisions**

CMD Collectibles seeks to reasonably protect the privacy of its online users. We encourage you to read this privacy policy carefully, so you will clearly understand our methods of collecting and using information.

We will not release your personal data to anyone else without your consent, unless we believe in good faith that we are required to do so by law or that the information must be disclosed to defend or bring a legal action.

We are not responsible for the information practices of third parties.

**Collection & Use of Information**

CMD Collectibles regularly collects information that visitors to our site voluntarily provide. Identifying information, such as name, street address, city, state, ZIP code and email address, is gathered at certain interactive areas on the site, such as when an individual subscribes to our mailing list. If you order a product, we collect additional information, some of which is nonpublic and some of which may come from third party sources.

We may use "cookies" as part of our site design, but you do have to accept cookies to use our site. We may record and use visitor IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track movements within our site and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use, but we do not track the usage patterns of identifiable individual users.

You may remove yourself from mailing lists at any time by contacting us by telephone, email or postal mail. CMD Collectibles does not collect your email address unless you voluntarily submit it to us or choose to communicate with us via email. We do not sell or rent any email addresses.

**Third-Party Service Providers**

CMD Collectibles may engage third-party vendors to help us manage our website and allow us to better serve our clients. With only the exceptions stated in this policy, we do not share with third parties any personally identifiable information you provide.

We may allow access to our database, including information you have provided, by third parties that provide us with services such as technical maintenance, but only to the extent necessary to provide users with the features of our site. If you purchase from us, you consent to our sharing with appropriate third parties such identity, delivery address, age verification, and payment method information as may be required to process your order.

**Security Measures**

CMD Collectibles endeavors to expose your personal information only to those with a legitimate reason for access. Our site, our hosted servers, and computers have technical and organizational security measures intended to protect the information under our control from accidental or unlawful destruction or accidental loss, alteration, and from unauthorized disclosure or access. Such measures do not guarantee prevention of loss, misuse, or alteration of information, and we cannot warrant the security of information you transmit to us. You are responsible for maintaining the privacy and confidentiality of your user name and password.

  **Links to Other Sites**

The CMD Collectibles website may have links to other sites we think may be of interest to our visitors. The purpose is to provide our clients with convenient access to other sites that might interest them. A link to another site does not imply an endorsement of the site's content or services. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of sites we do not own or operate. We encourage you to read the privacy statements at any such site that collects personally identifiable data.

**Updating or Correcting Personal Information; Privacy Policy Issues**

If you wish to review or modify your personally identifiable information, or if you have any questions or concerns about the content or application of this Privacy Policy, please notify us by email to [info@figpin.com](mailto:info@figpin.com).

**Policy Changes**

By using any feature of our website, you signify that you assent to this Privacy Policy as it may be amended from time to time. Neither this Privacy Policy nor your assent to it creates any contractual or other legal right. This Privacy Policy may change without notice.
